pods.com 2018-08-15

# Privacy Policy | PODS

**Introduction.  PODS ENTERPRISES, LLC **("PODS", “we” or "us") respects your privacy and we are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this privacy policy. This privacy policy (together with our terms of use at www.pods.com/Terms-Conditions.aspx and any other documents referred to in it) describes the types of information that we may collect from you or that you may provide us and our practices for collecting, using, protecting and disclosing that information.  This policy applies to information we collect on this website www.pods.com (our “Website”), in email, text or other electronic messages between you and us, through our call center, through mobile applications, and when you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy.

Please read our privacy policy terms carefully before using this Website, or providing us with personal information, to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. By accessing or using our Website or providing us with personal information, you agree to the terms set forth in this policy. This Privacy Policy is not a contract and does not create any legal rights or obligations. Rather, the following are guidelines for protecting the information you provide to us. Please refrain from using our Website or providing us with personal information if you disagree with anything stated below.

**Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It.   **We collect several types of information from you, including information:

  * By which you may be personally identified, such as name, e-mail address, mailing address, telephone number, credit card information, your responses to our survey questions, and information relating to any orders you place (“personal information”);
  * About your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details; and
  * That is about you but individually does not identify you, such technical and navigational information. This type of information may include computer browser type, internet protocol (IP) address, operating system, pages visited and time spent on our Website, and other communication data.

**How We Use Your Information.   **We may use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information, in the following ways: responding to your inquiries, providing you with information about our products and services that you request from us or other information that you find useful (regardless if a business relationship exists between us), aggregate statistics about our customer’s preferences, processing orders you have submitted, maintaining your account, to carry out obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us or to which we are entitled under applicable law, to carry out any other purposes which are permitted or required under applicable law, or which are disclosed to you and to which you consent. To ensure that you receive any e-mails that we may send to you, confirmations may be sent to us or our service provider when you open such emails or click certain email links. These confirmations may also show whether your e-mail application supports graphics so we can tailor our messages to you.

The information we collect about you may also be used or analyzed by us to improve our web design and functionality, show our ads on sites across the internet, enhance our ability to service you, and estimate our audience size and usage patterns. For the same reasons, we may also obtain other non-personally identifiable information about your general internet usage by using cookies. We may share non-personally identifiable information with third parties in connection with referral relationships and for reasons stated herein.

We use Google’s Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online. Third party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites across the internet. We and third party vendors, including Google, use first party cookies and third party cookies together to inform, optimize and serve ads based on visits to our website.

Occasionally, we may use your personal information to deliver marketing and account information relevant to you, such as discount coupons, information about new product offerings, reservation confirmations, surveys, account information, notification services, and for administrative reasons.

By providing your cellular number, where permitted by law, you agree to permit PODS to contact you by text messaging or by using an automatic telephone dialing system and/or a prerecorded voice regarding matters relevant to your account, including, without limitation, estimated time of arrivals and pickups of container(s), status of your contract, accounts payable and gypsy moth documentation, as applicable, and any other operational or account matters.

**Disclosure of Your Information**.  We will share your personal information with third parties only in ways that are described in this privacy policy.  Specifically, we may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide us:

  * To our franchises, subsidiaries and affiliates for the purposes of providing services;
  * To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business and to perform a variety of functions, such as fulfilling orders, billing and collection, assisting with marketing and promotions, credit card processing, transportation services, conducting contests or sweepstakes, helping us improve our product and service offerings and our website, providing technical services for our Website, data analytics, etc.  Such third parties are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of PODS' assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by PODS about our Website users is among the assets transferred.
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
  * To our carefully selected service providers to market their products or services to you if we believe that their respective products or services may be of interest to you (e.g., packing and loading services).
  * With your consent.
  * As permitted or required by applicable law.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * To comply with any court order, law or legal process (e.g., subpoenas), including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of PODS, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information**.

  * _Promotional Offers From PODS_.  You may opt-out of receiving any of our marketing or promotional emails at any time by sending an e-mail to [optout@pods.com](mailto:optout@pods.com)stating your request or by using the links provided in any commercial emails received from us.
  * _Disclosure of Your Information for Third-Party Advertising_. If you do not want us to share your personal information with an unaffiliated third party for promotional services, you can opt-out at any time by sending an email to [optout@pods.com](mailto:optout@pods.com) stating your request.
  * _Tracking Technologies and Advertising_.  You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. If you want to opt-out of receiving some advertising cookies (including LiveRamp’s use of cookies), please visit http://optout.aboutads.info. In addition, you can opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting Google's [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated).  If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.  Certain advertisers (including Google) may be members of NAI and/or the Digital Advertising Alliance.  You may opt out from advertiser’s services here: http:www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ or at the following link: www.aboutads.info/choices.

**Do-Not-Track Signals.  **Some web browsers may transmit "do-not-track" signals to websites with which the browser communicates. Currently, there is no standard that governs what, if anything, websites should do when they receive these signals. PODS currently does not take action in response to these signals.

**Providing Online Support.  **We may provide online customer service chat sessions to assist you while you are navigating through our Website. We will use and maintain any personal information you provide via these sessions in accordance with this privacy policy. We and our 3rd party service provider of the online customer chat feature may maintain dialogue transcripts of the online chats with us for staff training, for quality assurance purposes or for other purposes as described herein.

**Minors.  **We do not knowingly collect personal information from minors and ask that children under 18 years of age, or the age of majority in their jurisdiction of residence, do not submit personal information on our Website without parental consent. Although we cannot prevent children under 18 from submitting personal information, we will destroy such information if we are made aware that proper consent was not given.

**Other Websites.  **Many PODS operating areas are owned by franchisees that operate as independent businesses. Some franchisees also operate their own websites. This policy does not cover these other sites. We encourage franchisees to adopt similar privacy policies and practices as our privacy policy. However, please review the privacy policy of the other websites to understand their policies and practices regarding your personal information and how they will treat it.

**Accessing and Correcting Your Personal Information.  **You may request access to information on record with PODS at any time which has been collected about you. We permit and encourage you to request that any inaccuracies in your personal information be corrected or that such personal information be removed from our databases.

To make any request described above, send an e-mail to [accountmanager@pods.com ](mailto:optout@pods.com)or write to:

PODS Enterprises, LLC  
5585 Rio Vista Drive  
Clearwater, Florida 33760  
1-888-776-7637

When contacting us, please be sure to provide us with your exact e-mail address, name, address and/or telephone number(s) in order to be sure we handle your request correctly.  We may require you to verify your identify before allowing you to access your personal information.  We will use reasonable efforts to comply with your request; however, in some cases, we may not be able to allow you to access certain personal information in certain circumstances (e.g., if it contains personal information of other persons, or for legal reasons).

**Security.  **PODS recognizes your personal data is your private information, so we have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, and disclosure. Our Website uses encryption technology to help keep your personal information safe. Whenever you provide information, we use secure socket layer (“SSL”) technology to make sure that it is "encrypted," or, scrambled, so that no one else can read it while it is being transmitted over the Internet.  Personal information may be accessed by persons within our organization, or our third party service providers, who require such access to carry out the purposes indicated above, or such other purposes as may be permitted or required by the applicable law.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to us. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. You should always safeguard your own personal information by protecting passwords used to access websites and by safely disposing of records no longer needed.

**Users Outside of the United States**.  Some or all of the personal information we collect may be stored or processed on servers outside your jurisdiction of residence whose data protection laws may differ from the jurisdiction in which you live.  As a result, this information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in those jurisdictions according to laws in those jurisdictions.

**Changes.  **PODS reserves the right, in its discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this privacy policy at any time. You should check this page periodically for changes to this privacy policy. Your continued use of our Website following the posting of changes to this privacy policy will mean that you accept those changes.

**Contact Information.**  To ask questions or comments about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at:

PODS Enterprises, LLC  
Attn: Webmaster  
5585 Rio Vista Drive  
Clearwater, Florida 33760  
1-888-776-7637  

**Updated:**  May 30, 2018
